Hello friends, how are you all? Welcome
back to my channel. Friends,
I had uploaded a question in my video.
In the comments, it was asked that when we, suppose,
purchase a second hand car from someone, then after purchasing, will
we have to take new insurance
or the insurance that is already running in the
name of the first owner, can we
transfer it to our name or not? So,
this question is very important
and I hope that many people will also have this query in their mind. So,
if you like the video,
please like, share and
subscribe to the channel. So, friends, if
suppose you purchase a second hand car from someone, then
after purchasing, the
current assisting insurance
policy in his name will be easily transferred to your name. There is no
problem
and you also get time in this. The
validity of the time is 14
days. When the car is transferred to your name, then
you will get 14 days or two weeks from then.
You can
easily contact the insurance company and get the process done in your name.
When you do this, then one
thing you will have to pay is a small add-on fee for the
remaining
policy which is already running in the name of that owner
because see what will happen if
you suppose you do not get the insurance transferred in your name,
okay, and you do
not even take the insurance policy, if some
accident happens etc. then how will you claim it from the
insurance company, then
your claim will not be anything, you will get zero,
okay, so that is why you will have to pay the
fee for small correction because the
name, the personal information, that would
already be running in the name of the first owner,
now you have to
give your information, you have to get it transferred in your name,
for that you will get 14 days time
and after giving the endorsement premium you will have to
pay a small fee for the remaining policy,
okay, only after all this process is done, the
policy, the existing
policy will be transferred in your name.  It will be
transferred, right, and please get it done
because it
is very important to have insurance and it is mandatory from the government's side anyway.
Look brother, without
insurance, you cannot drive any two-wheeler or four-
wheeler on the road, a
separate penalty will be levied for it. Right, so hope
you guys liked this small information.
If you have any other query, you
can ask in the comment section. If you guys
liked the video, then please
like, share and subscribe to the channel.
Thank you so much. Jai Hind.